zoomgallery.com 2005-11-18

# ZoomGallery.com : Zoom At Things From Different Perspective Through Travel Photography.

ZoomGallery.com respect and are committed to protecting visitors privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, guest book and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by ZoomGallery.com The following discloses ZoomGallery.com Privacy Policy. 

**Information that Zoomgallery.com collects when you register for services on the site.**  
Zoomgallery.com offers access to Guest Book and newsletter that require registration. Your registration contact information may be used to send notification to you of ZoomGallery.com update and affiliates/advertisers links by e-mail. ZoomGallery.com DOES NOT share that information with other third party. 

Besides e-mail address, Zoomgallery.com also collect web site URL but name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you. ZoomGallery.com maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy and DO NOT sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

ZoomGallery.com may from time to time send e-mail announcing updated news/images/articles on the site. Except as stated above, Zoomgallery.com will not send you e-mail that you have not agreed to receive. 

**Cookies**  
From time to time, ZoomGallery.com or its affiliates/advertisers may send a cookie to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of Zoomgallery.com web page you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at ZoomGallery.com's may be diminished. 

**Opt-in announcement List Privacy Policy**  
When you sign up for a ZoomGallery.com e-mail newsletter, you are given the opportunity to also receive announcement lists from affiliates/advertiser. Whether you want to receive these announcement lists is your choice; you should only receive those lists you affirmatively choose to. If you choose to receive a specific announcement list, you will receive commercial messages that are related to the topic of the list from independent third parties that have affiliated with ZoomGallery.com. You may stop the arrival of these announcement lists at any time by removing your e-mail address from the list by following the instructions on the e-mails you receive. **  **

**Links to third party and you privacy policy.**  
ZoomGallery.com website contains many hyperlinks and advertisements to third party Web sites. Zoomgallery.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party Web sites or advertisers. Zoomgallery.com does not share any of the individual personal information you provide ZoomGallery.com with the third parties to which ZoomGallery.com links, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although Zoomgallery.com may share general, aggregate data with such third parties (such as how many people use our site). 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. **  **

**Your Consent To This Agreement**  
By using the ZoomGallery.com website, you consent to the collection and use of information by ZoomGallery.com as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
